University of Connecticut 1998.0189
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VI:, 1988
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1537-1538)
    - Minorities: Black Employees Association (Box 33:, Folder 1539)
    - Minorities: Day of Pride (Box 33:, Folder 1540)
    - Modern and Classical Languages (Box 33:, Folder 1541)
    - Museum, Benton (Box 33:, Folder 1542)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 33:, Folder 1543)
    - Music: Accreditation (Box 33:, Folder 1544)
    - Music: Marching Band (Box 33:, Folder 1545)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 33:, Folder 1546-1547)
    - Parking (Box 33:, Folder 1548)
    - Personnel (Box 33:, Folder 1549)
    - Planning (Box 33:, Folder 1550)
    - Police (Box 33:, Folder 1551)
    - Positions (PCs) (Box 33:, Folder 1552)
    - President's Retreat (Box 33:, Folder 1553)
    - Provost (Box 33:, Folder 1554)
    - Psychology: Accreditation (Box 33:, Folder 1555)
    - Publications (Box 33:, Folder 1556)
    - Puerto Rican Concerns (Box 33:, Folder 1557)
    - Racism: Asian Students, January - June (Box 33:, Folder 1558-1560)
    - Racism: Asian Students, July (Box 33:, Folder 1561-1563)
    - Racism: Asian Students, August - December (Box 33:, Folder 1564-1567)
    - Racism: Asian Students: Reports from Other Universities (Box 33:, Folder 1568-1570)
    - Regional Campuses
      - Branford House (Box 33:, Folder 1571)
      - Hartford (Box 33:, Folder 1572)
      - Southeastern (Box 33:, Folder 1573-1574)
      - Stamford (Box 33:, Folder 1575)
      - Stamford, Cresap Study (Box 34:, Folder 1576-1577)
      - Stamford, Downtown (Box 34:, Folder 1578)
      - Torrington (Box 34:, Folder 1579)
      - Waterbury (Box 34:, Folder 1580)
    - Regional Campuses: Fall Visits
      - Hartford (Box 34:, Folder 1581)
      - Southeastern (Box 34:, Folder 1582)
      - Stamford (Box 34:, Folder 1583)
      - Torrington (Box 34:, Folder 1584)
      - Waterbury (Box 34:, Folder 1585)
    - Regional Campuses: Spring Visits
      - Avery Point (Box 34:, Folder 1586)
      - Hartford (Box 34:, Folder 1587)
      - Litchfield County Center (Box 34:, Folder 1588)
      - Stamford (Box 34:, Folder 1589)
      - Torrington (Box 34:, Folder 1590)
      - Waterbury (Box 34:, Folder 1591)
    - Research Consultant: John Lee (Box 34:, Folder 1592)
    - Research and Development Corporation (Box 34:, Folder 1593)
    - Research Foundation (Box 34:, Folder 1594)
    - Retirement, mandatory (Box 34:, Folder 1595)
    - Retreat (November 15) (Box 34:, Folder 1596)
    - ROTC: Air Force (Box 34:, Folder 1597)
    - Salaries (Box 34:, Folder 1598)
    - Salaries: Management Studies (Box 34:, Folder 1599-1601)
    - Senate (Box 34:, Folder 1602)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 34:, Folder 1603)
    - Space Allocation (Box 34:, Folder 1604-1606)
    - Statistics (Box 34:, Folder 1607)
    - Student Affairs (Box 34:, Folder 1608)
    - Student Affairs: Meal Plans, Seven - Day (Box 34:, Folder 1609)
    - Student Affairs: New Residence Hall Construction (Box 34:, Folder 1610)
    - Student Affairs: Residence Hall Security (Box 34:, Folder 1611)
    - Student Organizations
      - BiGala (Box 34:, Folder 1612)
      - ConnPirg (Box 34:, Folder 1613)
      - Daily Campus (Box 34:, Folder 1614)
      - Graduate Student Senate (Box 34:, Folder 1615)
      - Nutmeg (Box 34:, Folder 1616)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (Box 34:, Folder 1617)
    - Task Force on Program Development at Avery Point - Final Report (Box 34:, Folder 1618)
    - Task Labor (Box 34:, Folder 1619)
    - Telecommunications (Box 34:, Folder 1620)
    - Transportation (Box 34:, Folder 1621)
    - Tuition/Fees (Box 34:, Folder 1622)
    - UCEPI (Box 34:, Folder 1623-1626)
    - UConn Foundation (Box 34:, Folder 1627-1629)
      - Congressional Correspondence
        - Dodd (Box 36:, Folder 1703)
        - Gejdenson (Box 36:, Folder 1704)
        - Johnson (Box 36:, Folder 1705)
        - Kennelly (Box 36:, Folder 1706)
        - Morrison (Box 36:, Folder 1707)
        - Rowland (Box 36:, Folder 1708)
        - Shays (Box 36:, Folder 1709)
        - Weicker (Box 36:, Folder 1710)
    - UConn Foundation: Agreed Upon Procedures Report, 7/1/87 - 6/30/88 (Box 35:, Folder 1630)
    - UConn Foundation: Signatory (Box 35:, Folder 1631)
    - University Medals (Box 35:, Folder 1632)
    - Water Resources Institute (Box 35:, Folder 1633)
    - Women's Center (Box 35:, Folder 1634)
  - State Government (Blue Files)
    - Administrative Services (Box 35:, Folder 1635)
    - Administrative Services: Disaster Recovery (Box 35:, Folder 1636)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 35:, Folder 1637)
    - Attorney General (Box 35:, Folder 1638)
    - Auditor
      - Abuse of Tuition Reimbursement Policy (Box 35:, Folder 1639)
        (Public Safety)
      - Associated Student Government, Avery Point, 1986-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1640)
      - Associated Student Government, Stamford, 1986-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1641)
      - Athletics - Tardy Deposits (Box 35:, Folder 1642)
      - Audit Report Period Ended June, 1983 (Box 35:, Folder 1643)
      - Fiscal Year, 1986-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1644)
      - Bursar - Timely Deposits (Box 35:, Folder 1645)
      - Daily Campus Student Activity Fund (Box 35:, Folder 1646)
      - Delays in Requesting Federal Reimbursement (Box 35:, Folder 1647)
      - Health Center (Box 35:, Folder 1648-1649)
      - Health Center - Foundation (Box 35:, Folder 1650-1651)
      - Health Center - Management of Facilities Projects and Materials (Box 35:, Folder 1652)
      - Law School - Student Bar Association (Box 35:, Folder 1653)
      - Mannheim Student Exchange Program (Box 35:, Folder 1654)
      - Star Copier (Box 35:, Folder 1655)
      - Torrington - Associated Student Government Activity Fund and Snack Bar Fund (Box 35:, Folder 1656)
      - Uncas on Thames (Box 35:, Folder 1657)
    - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 35:, Folder 1658)
    - Connecticut High Education Supplemental Town Authority (Box 35:, Folder 1659)
    - Controller (Box 35:, Folder 1660)
    - DHE
      - December (Box 35:, Folder 1661-1662)
      - November (Box 35:, Folder 1663-1664)
      - October (Box 35:, Folder 1665-1666)
      - September (Box 35:, Folder 1667)
      - August (Box 35:, Folder 1668)
      - July (Box 35:, Folder 1669)
      - June (Box 35:, Folder 1670)
      - May (Box 35:, Folder 1671)
      - April (Box 35:, Folder 1672-1673)
      - March (Box 35:, Folder 1674)
      - February (Box 35:, Folder 1675)
      - January (Box 35:, Folder 1676)
      - Admissions Practices and Housing Availability (Box 35:, Folder 1677)
      - Fairfield County Study (Box 35:, Folder 1678)
      - Minority Advancement and Staff Development Programs (Box 35:, Folder 1679)
      - Mission Statements (Box 35:, Folder 1680)
      - Off - Campus Offerings (Box 36:, Folder 1681)
      - Research Funding (Box 36:, Folder 1682-1683)
      - Waterbury (Box 36:, Folder 1684)
    - Economic Development (Box 36:, Folder 1685)
    - Education (Box 36:, Folder 1686)
    - Environmental Protection (Box 36:, Folder 1687)
    - Fiscal Analysis (Box 36:, Folder 1688)
    - Governor (Box 36:, Folder 1689)
    - Historical Commission (Box 36:, Folder 1690)
    - Human Resources (Box 36:, Folder 1691)
    - Legislative Inquiries (Box 36:, Folder 1692)
    - Personnel (Box 36:, Folder 1693)
    - Policy and Management (Box 36:, Folder 1694)
    - Policy and Management: Grand List Study (Box 36:, Folder 1695-1697)
    - Policy and Management: Outside Consultants (Box 36:, Folder 1698)
    - Program Review and Investigation Committee (Box 36:, Folder 1699)
    - Public Works (Box 36:, Folder 1700)
    - Transportation (Box 36:, Folder 1701)
    - Veterans' Affairs (Box 36:, Folder 1702)
  - Federal Government (Green Files)
    - Constitutional Bicentennial (Box 36:, Folder 1711)
    - Education Department (Box 36:, Folder 1712)
    - Friday Commission Report (Box 36:, Folder 1713)
    - Health and Human Services (Box 36:, Folder 1714)
    - International Development Agency (Box 36:, Folder 1715)
    - Navy (Box 36:, Folder 1716)
    - Postal Services (Box 36:, Folder 1717)
  - Organizations (Black Files)
    - Aetna Institute (Box 36:, Folder 1718)
    - American Festival Theatre, Stratford (Box 36:, Folder 1719-1721)
    - Questionnaires (Box 36:, Folder 1722)
    - Science Park, New Haven (Box 36:, Folder 1723)
    - Tolland Foundation (Box 36:, Folder 1724)
    - United Way (Box 36:, Folder 1725)
    - Windham Hospital (Box 36:, Folder 1726)
    - Yale University (Box 36:, Folder 1727)
  - Education Associations (Yellow Files)
    - ACE (Box 36:, Folder 1728)
    - American Association for Higher Education (Box 36:, Folder 1729)
    - Connecticut Academy of Science and Engineering (Box 36:, Folder 1730)
    - Council of Presidents (Box 36:, Folder 1731-1733)
    - NASULGC (Box 36:, Folder 1734)
    - NASULGC: Annual Meeting (Box 36:, Folder 1735)
    - NEASC (Box 36:, Folder 1736)
    - NEBHE (Box 36:, Folder 1737-1738)
- Series VII:, 1989
  - University Files (Red Files)
    - Administration: Property Consideration (Box 37:, Folder 1739)
      - Recycling (Box 37:, Folder 1740)
      - Texaco Lease (Box 37:, Folder 1741)
      - Vice President (Box 37:, Folder 1742-1743)
    - Admissions (Box 37:, Folder 1747)
      - Director Search (Box 37:, Folder 1748)
      - Inquiries (Box 37:, Folder 1749)
      - Renovations (Box 37:, Folder 1750)
      - Reports (Box 37:, Folder 1751)
    - Affirmative Action (Box 37:, Folder 1752-1759)
      - Advisory Committee (Box 37:, Folder 1760)
      - Diversity Training (Box 37:, Folder 1761)
    - African - American Cultural Center (Box 37:, Folder 1762)
    - Aging, Travelers Center on (Box 37:, Folder 1763)
    - Agriculture (Box 37:, Folder 1764)
      - Dairy/Creamery Operations (Box 37:, Folder 1765-1766)
      - Dairy Bar/Creamery Petitions (Box 37:, Folder 1767)
      - Holcomb/Granby Property (Box 37:, Folder 1768-1769)
    - Agriculture and Natural Resources (Box 37:, Folder 1770)
      - Pathobiology Dedication (Box 37:, Folder 1771)
    - AIDS (Box 37:, Folder 1772)
    - Alcohol/Drugs (Box 37:, Folder 1773-1774)
    - Allied Health (Box 38:, Folder 1775-1777)
    - Alternate Retirement/Social Security (Box 38:, Folder 1778)
    - Alumni: A - W (Box 38:, Folder 1779-1800)
      - Distinguished Alumni Awards (Box 38:, Folder 1801)
      - Margin for Excellence (Box 38:, Folder 1802)
    - Alumni Association (Box 38:, Folder 1803-1805)
      - Alumni House (Box 38:, Folder 1806)
      - Black Alumni Association (Box 38:, Folder 1807)
      - Excellence Awards (Box 38:, Folder 1808)
    - Animal Care (Box 38:, Folder 1809)
    - Annual Report (Box 38:, Folder 1810)
    - Anonymous Letters (Box 38:, Folder 1811)
    - Appointment Letter Problems (Box 38:, Folder 1812)
    - Architecture, School of (Box 38:, Folder 1813)
    - Archives: China Project (Box 38:, Folder 1814)
    - Archives Building (Cross Reference Dodd Papers ( Green Files) and Project Judaica ( Red Files) (Box 38:, Folder 1815)
    - Asian - American Faculty Association (Box 38:, Folder 1816)
    - Athletics
      - Advisory Committee (Box 38:, Folder 1817)
      - Basketball (Box 38:, Folder 1818)
      - Complementary Ticket Policy (Box 38:, Folder 1819)
      - CPIA (Box 38:, Folder 1820)
      - Crew Club (Box 38:, Folder 1821)
      - Drug Testing (Box 38:, Folder 1822)
      - Football (Box 38:, Folder 1823)
      - Gampel Opening (Box 38:, Folder 1824)
      - NCAA (Box 38:, Folder 1825-1827)
      - Sports Center (Box 38:, Folder 1828-1829)
      - Sports Center Parking (Box 38:, Folder 1830)
      - Task Force (Box 38:, Folder 1831)
      - Ticket Priority Seating Locations (Box 38:, Folder 1832)
      - Yankee Conference (Box 38:, Folder 1833)
    - Attorney (Box 38:, Folder 1834)
    - Audit Subcommittee (Box 38:, Folder 1835)
    - Auditor (Box 38:, Folder 1836)
      - Activity Report, 1988 (Box 38:, Folder 1837)
      - Environmental Health and Safety Office Search (Box 38:, Folder 1838)
      - Graduate Student Senate (Box 38:, Folder 1839)
      - President's Residence, Equipment Replacement (Box 38:, Folder 1840)
      - Special Local Fund (Box 38:, Folder 1841)
    - Auditorium (Box 39:, Folder 1842)
    - Auditorium: Director Search (Box 39:, Folder 1843)
    - Biobehavioral Science (Box 39:, Folder 1844)
    - Biology (Box 39:, Folder 1845)
    - Biotechnology (Box 39:, Folder 1846)
    - Black Studies (Box 39:, Folder 1847)
    - Bomb Threats (Box 39:, Folder 1848)
    - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 39:, Folder 1849-1852)
    - Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 39:, Folder 1853-1856)
    - Budget
      - Early Retirement (Box 39:, Folder 1857)
      - Five-Year Equipment Plan (Box 39:, Folder 1858)
      - Position Refills (Box 39:, Folder 1859)
      - Salary Freezes (Box 39:, Folder 1860)
      - Temporary Labor (Box 39:, Folder 1861)
      - Tuition Fund (Box 39:, Folder 1862)
    - Bursar (Box 39:, Folder 1863)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 39:, Folder 1864-1865)
    - Small Business Development Center (Box 39:, Folder 1866)
    - By-Laws (Box 39:, Folder 1867)
    - Center for Educational Innovation (Box 39:, Folder 1868)
    - Center for Public Management (Box 39:, Folder 1869)
    - Chemistry Department (Box 39:, Folder 1870)
    - Child Development Lab (Box 39:, Folder 1871)
    - Collective Bargaining (Box 39:, Folder 1872-1876)
    - Commencement (Box 39:, Folder 1877)
    - Committees (Box 39:, Folder 1878)
    - Communication Science (Box 39:, Folder 1879)
    - Computer Center (Box 39:, Folder 1880-1881)
    - ConnTech (Box 39:, Folder 1882)
    - ConnTech: Beecham (Box 39:, Folder 1883)
    - Convocation (Box 39:, Folder 1884)
    - Co-op (Box 39:, Folder 1885)
    - Cooperative Education (Box 39:, Folder 1886)
    - Cooperative Program: Public Affairs (Central) (Box 39:, Folder 1887)
    - Dental Medicine (Box 39:, Folder 1888)
    - Development (Box 40)
      - A - H (Box 40:, Folder 1889)
      - K - M (Box 40:, Folder 1890)
      - P - Z (Box 40:, Folder 1891)
      - Aetna (Box 40:, Folder 1892)
      - Brakely Feasibility Studies (Box 40:, Folder 1893)
      - CBIA (Box 40:, Folder 1894)
      - Dinners (Box 40:, Folder 1895)
      - General Electric (Box 40:, Folder 1896)
      - Grant Proposals (Box 40:, Folder 1897)
      - IBM (Box 40:, Folder 1898)
      - Klebanoff (Box 40:, Folder 1899)
      - Kresge (Box 40:, Folder 1900)
      - Max Putzel (Box 40:, Folder 1901)
    - Economics Department (Box 40:, Folder 1902)
    - Education, School of (Box 40:, Folder 1903)
    - Education, School of: Disabilities Act (Box 40:, Folder 1904)
    - Educational Innovation, Center for (Box 40:, Folder 1905)
    - Emergency Preparedness (Box 40:, Folder 1906)
    - Endowed Chairs (Box 40:, Folder 1907)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 40:, Folder 1908)
    - Engineering (Box 40:, Folder 1909-1912)
    - English Department (Box 40:, Folder 1913)
    - English: Connecticut Writing Project (Box 40:, Folder 1914-1918)
    - Enrollment (Box 40:, Folder 1919)
    - Environmental Health and Safety (Box 40:, Folder 1920)
    - Exchange Programs
      - China (Box 40:, Folder 1921)
      - El Salvador (Box 40:, Folder 1922)
      - Greece (Box 40:, Folder 1923)
      - Maastricht (Box 40:, Folder 1924)
      - Nova Scotia (Box 40:, Folder 1925)
      - Poland (Box 40:, Folder 1926)
      - Poland, Gierowski Visit (Box 40:, Folder 1927)
      - Poland, Warsaw Technical University (Box 40:, Folder 1928)
      - Turkey (Box 40:, Folder 1929)
    - Executive Compensation (Box 40:, Folder 1930)
    - Extended and Continuing Education (Box 40:, Folder 1931)
    - External Affairs (Box 40:, Folder 1932)
    - Equipment Maintenance Fee (Box 40:, Folder 1933)
    - Facilities (Box 40:, Folder 1934-1936)
    - Faculty Alumni Center (Box 41:, Folder 1937)
    - Family Studies (Box 41:, Folder 1938)
    - Finance: Financial Aid (Box 41:, Folder 1939)
    - Finance: Vice President Jones (Box 41:, Folder 1940-1941)
    - Fine Arts (Box 41:, Folder 1942-1944)
    - Fraternities/Sororities (Box 41:, Folder 1945)
    - Government Relations (Box 41:, Folder 1946-1948)
    - Graduate School (Box 41:, Folder 1949)
    - Grants and Contracts (Box 41:, Folder 1950)
    - Greek Chapel and Cultural Center (Box 41:, Folder 1951)
    - Harassment (Box 41:, Folder 1952)
    - Hazardous Duty Retirement (Box 41:, Folder 1953)
    - Health Center (Box 41:, Folder 1954-1957)
      - External Funds Management (Box 41:, Folder 1958)
      - Hospital Support Building (Box 41:, Folder 1959-1960)
      - John Dempsey Hospital (Box 41:, Folder 1961)
      - Misconduct in Research (Box 41:, Folder 1962)
      - Mount Sinai (Box 41:, Folder 1963)
      - New Samaritan Corp. (see also Travelers Center, Aging) (Box 41:, Folder 1964)
      - Newington Children's Hospital (Box 41:, Folder 1965)
      - Outside Consultants (Box 41:, Folder 1966)
      - Pediatrics Research Training (Box 41:, Folder 1967)
      - Helen Smits Salary (Box 41:, Folder 1968)
      - Tuition Transfer (Box 41:, Folder 1969)
      - Uncas on Thames (Box 41:, Folder 1970)
      - Newington Children's Hospital (Box 41:, Folder 1971)
    - History Department (Box 41:, Folder 1972)
    - Honors Program (Box 41:, Folder 1973)
    - Housing (Box 41:, Folder 1974)
    - Human Relations Proposal (Box 41:, Folder 1974)
    - Identification Cards: User Fee (Box 41:, Folder 1975)
    - Indirect Cost Recoveries (Box 41:, Folder 1976)
    - Institute of Materials Science (Box 41:, Folder 1977)
    - Institutional Relations (Box 42:, Folder 1978)
    - Institutional Research (Box 42:, Folder 1979-1980)
    - International Programs (Box 42:, Folder 1981)
    - Interview: David Morse (Box 42:, Folder 1982)
    - Jewish Matters (Box 42:, Folder 1983)
    - Judaic Studies (Box 42:, Folder 1984)
    - Labor Education Advising Committee (Box 42:, Folder 1985)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 42:, Folder 1986)
    - Latina Professors Women's Association (Box 42:, Folder 1987)
    - Law School (Box 42:, Folder 1988-1989)
      - Commencement (Box 42:, Folder 1990)
      - Foundation (Box 42:, Folder 1991)
      - Gallivan Chair (Box 42:, Folder 1992)
      - Library (Box 42:, Folder 1993)
    - Leave: Administrative, 1987-1989 (Box 42:, Folder 1994)
    - Liberal Arts: Dean Search (Box 42:, Folder 1995)
    - Liberal Arts: Science (Box 42:, Folder 1996)
    - Library (Box 42:, Folder 1997)
      - Archival Planning Committee (Box 42:, Folder 1998)
      - Friends of Library (Box 42:, Folder 1999)
      - Structural Concerns (Box 42:, Folder 2000)
    - Mail Services (Box 42:, Folder 2001)
    - Mansfield, Town of (Box 42:, Folder 2002)
    - Mansfield Training School (see also Space Allocation: Mts. and Child Development Lab) (Box 42:, Folder 2003)
    - Marine Sciences (Box 42:, Folder 2004)
    - Math Department (Box 42:, Folder 2005)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 42:, Folder 2006)
    - Medicine, School of Accreditation (Box 42:, Folder 2007)
    - Metanoia (Box 42:, Folder 2008)
    - Minorities
      - African - American (Box 42:, Folder 2009)
      - Black Employees Association (Box 42:, Folder 2010)
      - Center for Academic Programs (Box 42:, Folder 2011)
      - Day of Pride (Box 42:, Folder 2012)
    - Museum, Benton (Box 42:, Folder 2013-2014)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 42:, Folder 2015)
    - Music Department (Box 42:, Folder 2016-2017)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 42:, Folder 2018-2019)
    - Northwood Apartments (Box 42:, Folder 2020)
    - Ombudsman (Box 42:, Folder 2021)
    - Parents' Letters (Box 42:, Folder 2022)
    - Parking (Box 42:, Folder 2023-2025)
    - Peat Marwick Development Services (Box 42:, Folder 2026)
    - Personnel (Box 42:, Folder 2027-2028)
    - Pharmacy (Box 42:, Folder 2029-2030)
    - Photo Lab (Box 42:, Folder 2031)
    - Police (Box 42:, Folder 2032-2033)
    - Polish - Jewish Archives Project (Box 42:, Folder 2034-2035)
    - Political Science (Box 42:, Folder 2036)
    - Positions (PCs) (Box 42:, Folder 2037)
    - Publications (Box 42:, Folder 2038)
    - Purchasing (Box 42:, Folder 2039)
    - Racism (Box 42:, Folder 2040-2042)
    - Regional Campuses
      - Branford House (Box 42:, Folder 2043)
      - Hartford (Box 42:, Folder 2044)
      - Southeastern (Box 42:, Folder 2045)
      - Stamford (Box 42:, Folder 2046-2048)
      - Torrington (Box 42:, Folder 2049)
      - Waterbury (Box 42:, Folder 2050)
    - Regional Campuses: Spring Visits (Box 43)
      - Hartford (Box 43:, Folder 2051)
      - Southeastern (Box 43:, Folder 2052)
      - Stamford (Box 43:, Folder 2053)
      - Torrington (Box 43:, Folder 2054)
      - Waterbury (Box 43:, Folder 2055)
    - Research Consultant: John Lee (Box 43:, Folder 2056)
    - Research Foundation (Box 43:, Folder 2057)
    - Research Foundation: External Funds (Box 43:, Folder 2058-2060)
    - Retirement, Mandatory (Box 43:, Folder 2061)
    - ROTC (Box 43:, Folder 2062)
    - Salaries (Box 43:, Folder 2063-2066)
    - Senate (Box 43:, Folder 2067)
    - Senate: Subcommittee on Discriminatory Harassment (Box 43:, Folder 2068)
    - Signatory Authority (Box 43:, Folder 2069)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 43:, Folder 2070)
    - Space Allocation (Box 43:, Folder 2071-2072)
    - Student Affairs (Box 44)
      - Disabled Students (Box 44:, Folder 2073)
      - Disciplinary Actions (Box 44:, Folder 2074)
      - Health Services (Box 44:, Folder 2075)
      - Meal Plan (Seven - Day) (Box 44:, Folder 2076)
      - New Residence Hall Construction (Box 44:, Folder 2077)
      - Residence Halls - Substance - Free Floor (Box 44:, Folder 2078)
      - Residential Life (Box 44:, Folder 2079)
      - Residential Life - Dorm Shortfall (Box 44:, Folder 2080)
      - Sexual Preference (Box 44:, Folder 2081)
      - Special Populations Report (Box 44:, Folder 2082)
      - Student Conduct Code (Box 44:, Folder 2083)
      - Vendor Solicitations in Residence Halls (Box 44:, Folder 2084)
    - Student Organizations
      - ConnPirg (Box 44:, Folder 2085)
      - Graduate Student Senate (Box 44:, Folder 2086)
      - Undergraduate Student Government (USG) (Box 44:, Folder 2087)
      - WHUS (Box 44:, Folder 2088)
    - Task Force (Box 44:, Folder 2089)
    - Technology Center (Box 44:, Folder 2090)
    - Telecommunications (Box 44:, Folder 2091)
    - Telemedia (Box 44:, Folder 2092)
    - Temporary Labor (Box 44:, Folder 2093)
    - Transportation (Box 44:, Folder 2094)
    - Tuition/Fees (Box 44:, Folder 2095-2097)
    - UCEPI (Box 44:, Folder 2098-2102)
    - UConn Foundation
      - January - June (Box 44:, Folder 2103)
      - July - December (Box 44:, Folder 2104)
      - Annual Fund (Box 44:, Folder 2105)
      - Deficit (Box 44:, Folder 2106)
      - Fiduciary (Box 44:, Folder 2107)
      - Healy, John (Box 44:, Folder 2108)
      - Holding Account (Box 44:, Folder 2109)
      - Policies and Procedures (Box 44:, Folder 2110)
      - Research Foundation (Box 44:, Folder 2111)
      - Research Foundation - Accounts (Box 44:, Folder 2112)
      - Signatory (Box 44:, Folder 2113)
    - Vice Presidents (Box 44:, Folder 2114)
    - Women's Center (Box 44:, Folder 2115)
  - State Government (Blue Files)
    - Administrative Services (Box 44:, Folder 2116-2117)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 44:, Folder 2118)
    - Arts Commission (Box 44:, Folder 2119)
    - Attorney General (Box 44:, Folder 2120)
    - Auditors
      - Associated Student Commissaries (Box 44:, Folder 2121)
      - Graduate Student Council Activity Fund (Box 44:, Folder 2122)
      - Hartford Campus - Receipts Not Traced To Deposits (Box 44:, Folder 2123)
      - Health Center (Fiscal Years 1987-89) (Box 44:, Folder 2124)